In 1999, Ruden entered the Vietnamese market,
bringing with it over 150 years of experience in protecting the finances and
health of millions of families
worldwide.  With a
customer-centric philosophy,
Rudenal consistently strives for practical innovation
for its customers.  A prime example is innovating the
customer experience.  Rudencial collaborated with
experts and VN Express to
produce a series of articles on insurance: Understand it well,
buy the right one.  We help customers understand
their rights and implement
call recording for consultations to ensure customers purchase products
that meet their needs and financial capabilities. We are
also expanding our customer experience center model to provide fast and comprehensive service from consultation to contract management and claims processing. Furthermore, we are establishing
model general agency offices to meet the
ever-changing needs of our
customers and launching the Ring
Green Future unit-linked fund, the first unit-linked fund
in the Vietnamese life insurance market,
offering customers who own
unit-linked insurance products the
option to invest in
sustainable development, benefiting
them both today and in the future.  When
clients need rent the most, the
insurance claim processing
is quick to help them and their
families overcome difficulties.  In the
first half of 2025, Ruden made payments totaling
VND 7,410 billion, accounting for over 25% of the entire industry.
Brudential's customer-centric efforts have been recognized with
prestigious awards.
[Music]
We are also constantly improving the
quality of our consultants.  Regular,
intensive training and coaching sessions are organized
to help consultants improve their
expertise, sell effectively and efficiently, and build
long-term relationships with clients.  Brudental also
collaborates with the FSB Institute at
FBT University to implement a training program to
enhance corporate governance capabilities
for general agency office managers
and focuses on developing
MDRT consultants, a globally recognized title
for
leading professionals in the
life insurance and financial services fields with
outstanding expertise and skills, always
putting the client's best interests first.
Thanks to this, we achieved the number 1 position
in the Vietnamese market and 12th
globally in terms of the number of MDRT members.
Rudenal also innovates its
sustainable community development strategy with
smart finance projects and
safe school projects aimed at
improving financial literacy and
traffic safety for Vietnamese children.
We also work alongside the Vietnamese government
to achieve its goal of building a
green economy.  As a result, Rudenal has been
listed among sustainable businesses eight times in a row
.
Through practical innovations, Rudens has
helped millions of customers move towards a
better life.
Thanks to
that insurance policy, my child's life is the way it is
today.
He simply invested in buying insurance
so that later on, his fish would
n't be at a disadvantage compared to anyone else's.   He
still has his insurance money to cover his finances
.  He also hopes that
life will get better in the future.
Insurance is like a companion,
supporting you throughout the entire journey, from the
moment you fall until you fully
recover. Now, you've received the
insurance payout, enough to cover your
household expenses. 26
years of companionship, 26 years of continuous
innovation.  Thank you for trusting Rudenal
on your journey to protect your loved ones
and build a sustainable future.